(Leonard:)You cannot blow up my head
with your mind.
Then I'll settle for an aneurism.
(Penny:)- Stop it.
- You hit me.
You saw that. He hit me.
- You tried to blow up my head.
- So it was working.
(Leonard:)It wasn't... It was not...
You are a nutcase.
We'll see. Heads up, you people
in the front row. This is a splash zone.
Stop it. Stop it.
(Leonard:)Quit it.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
(Penny:)Is this usually
how these physics things go?
(Howard:)More often than you'd think.
Hit you with a Vulcan nerve pinch.
- No pinches. No...!
- No!
[LOCK CLICKING]
(Sheldon:)You could have offered me a ride home.
(Leonard:)You're lucky I didn't run you over.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand
what you're unhappy about.
(Sheldon:)You begged me to come, I came.
There's just no pleasing you.
(Leonard:)You're right. I'm the problem,
the one that needs help.